<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome on Rafa Alkalai</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome on Rafa Alkalai</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/books/</guid>
      <description>Bookshelf Below is a list of some of my favorite reads, this is not a comprehensive list nor is it static. You will also find what I’m currently enjoying.
Currently reading I am currently reading Finding The Mother Tree by Dr. Suzanne Simard. This fantastic memoir was written by UBC Professor Dr. Suzanne Simard on her journey uncovering some fantastical truths about our forests.
 Books I have enjoyed  Braiding Sweetgrass by Robin Wall Kimmerer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/</guid>
      <description>Under construction. Return later for some music recommendations!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Rafa</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Born and raised in Recife (Brazil) I now live in Vancouver on the traditional, unceded, and occupied territory of the xʷməθkʷəy̓əm, Sḵwx̱wú7mesh, and səlilwətaɬ peoples. After many years in Recife, I was granted the opportunity to finish my secondary education at the United World College Costa Rica, where I fell in love with the study of biodiversity at multiple scales.
Although currently I’m just an undergraduate student, I intend on pursuing a career in academic research and teaching.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
